(Sheldon:)You want to see it?
(Amy:)Can't you just tell me?
(Sheldon:)But I made a video.
(Sheldon(on video):)I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
(Sheldon(on video):)and I'd like to tell you
why I should be chosen to...
(echoing):
go to Mars!
(Sheldon(on video):)I'm exceedingly smart.
(Sheldon(on video):)I graduated college at 14.
(Sheldon(on video):)While my brother
was getting an STD
(Sheldon(on video):)I was getting a PhD.
(Sheldon(on video):)Penicillin can't take this away.
(Sheldon(on video):)Being in close quarters,
cleanliness is important
(Sheldon(on video):)and... my hygiene is impeccable.
(Sheldon(on video):)In fact, animals don't trust me
(Sheldon(on video):)because I smell like nothing.
(Sheldon:)Yeah...
(inhales)
(Sheldon(on video):)Literally nothing.
(Sheldon(on video):)During the seven-month
space flight,
(Sheldon(on video):)I can keep up morale
with my wacky sense of humor.
(Sheldon(on video):)Hey, Leonard...